# ROSICH MARCOS

**UNITY 3D ENVIRONMENT ARTIST** 

# SUMMARY

I am a 3D artist located in Argentina and focused in the production of game assets to be used in Unity3D.

I work with Blender and am used to creating unitypackages with preconfigured models, materials and animation avatars, so that they can be easily added to any Unity project.

Since 2020 i have been participating in group and personal projects that helped me develop a full workflow and prepare myself to get introduced into a professional work environment.

I am currently looking for a remote position as an artist in the game developing industry and willing to learn any additional software needed, as well as relocating to another place.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **3D CHARACTER ARTIST AND ANIMATOR**

Nightmare Project June 2020 - Present

- Coordinated a small team of artists, and fixed the topology of their models
- Rigged characters according to the Unity conventions and animated them.
- Succeeded at modeling and texturing the main character, following a model sheet provided by a team member.
- Cooperated closely with programmers and designers to obtain the best final results.

#### **GAME DEVELOPER**

Personal Projects and Game Jams August 2020 - Present

- Learnt to use Git, exporting from Unity to WebGL and setting up an html page for the game.
- Got experience in Unity optimization techniques such as "Draw Call Batching"
- Got familiarized with working against the clock

# ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

#### **SELF-TAUGHT**

Skill Set Developing June 2020 - Present

# UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA NACIONAL - RESISTENCIA, ARG

Game Developing Course - Introduction to Blender, MakeHuman and programming games in C# using Unity3D January 2020 - May 2020

### CONTACT INFO

- in linkedin.com/in/rosichmarcos
- mosichmarcos.com.ar
- rosichmarcos.artstation.com
- wa.me/5493404502729

#### SKILLS SET

- 3D Modelling
- UV Mapping
- Stylized Texture Painting
- Procedural Materials
- Texture and Normal Map Baking
- Unity Shader Graph
- Character and Prop Sculpting
- Retopologizing
- Exporting to Unity
- Unity Animation Controller Configuration
- .unitypackage Generation
- Version Controlling Using Git
- Basic C#
- Basic Rigging
- Basic Animating

#### SOFT SKILLS

- Feedback accepting
- Desiring to learn and to teach
- Communicative
- · Adaptability to the team and project
- Punctuality

#### LANGUAGE

- Spanish: Native
- English (2011-2017): Limited Working Proficiency